

Senior Graphic Designer & 3D Generalist Specialist with 7+ years of experience in the management of the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Expert at interdepartmental coordination and communication. Skilled with Adobe Creative Suite (Adobe XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, Aftereffects, InDesign), Able to stretch the boundaries of 3D Designing skills are Maya, 3ds Max and to help my client's brands stand out.

Vinay Kumar Saini

Phone:

+91 9398397923

E-Mail:

vinnu022@gmail.com

Website:

www.flyingbird3dstudio.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vinay-kumar-saini-654390a1/

Skill Highlights

Adobe XD UI & UX

Link 1: Design 1
Link 2: Design 2

- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- After Effects
- In Design
- Maya

Link 3: Showreel

Max

Languages

English Telugu Hindi

Experience

06/2020 to Present

Vollmond Innovations & Social Entrepreneurs Pvt Ltd.

- Cooperate with developers to create clean UI & UX interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Design project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed designing tasks for front end developers and internal websites as well as design logos

10/2018 to 05/2020

Rachnoutsav Events Pvt Ltd.

- Designed events & planned using 3D & 2D while managing all event project elements within allotted time limits.
- Maintained social media works like videos, flyers, logos Broachers etc.

06/2017 to 08/2018

RVRPRO Pvt Ltd.

• Design all required elements for event using maya & max

04/2016 to 05/2017

Bestbus Ads Pvt Ltd.

Coordinate with marketing manager & design all required elements for Ads

08/2015 to 05/2016

Sync Process Soft Tech Pvt Ltd.

• Complete detailed designing tasks for front end developers and internal websites as well as design logos

Education

Degree – B.Com Computers

Avanthi Degree College, Hyderabad.

64%

2011

2014

Intermediate - CEC

New Era Junior College, Hyderabad.

70%

2009

Secondary School

Krishnaveni Talent School, Mancherial.

65%

Certifications

Diploma in Visual Media (DVM)

Personal Details

FATHER'S NAME : Laxman Rao Saini

DATE OF BIRTH : 20-10-1992

MARITAL STATUS: Married

NATIONALITY : Indian

HOBBIES : Listening Music

ADDRESS : Kailash Hills, Kukatpally, Hyderabad.